♪Mighty winds carry me to the heavens♪
♪On a wild steed,
I sing, smiling at the mortal world♪
♪Then the cold night veils the stars♪
♪I fall to the depths, yet walk alone♪
♪I brave countless snowy peaks♪
♪Your lingering warmth still fills
my palm♪
♪Though frost and snow may bar my way♪
♪The light in my eyes will never fade♪
♪With a sword that cleaves the clouds♪
♪With a heart as firm as stone♪
♪Through all I've endured,
I have no regrets♪
♪I'm still the boy I once was♪
=Sword God=
=Episode 17=
What's wrong, Immortal Venerable?
This is the Heavenly Mystic Robe.
It's impervious to fire and water.
It's yours.
Put it on before you leave.
Where do I change?
Right here.
If you go out dressed like this,
won't it make us a laughingstock?
All right.
Then please give me some privacy.
Interesting.
Are you shy?
Fine.
This boy
will surely go far.
Eldest Senior Sister,
that handsome guy is pretty good, huh?
You like him too?
You think I'm like you?
I don't care.
If we ever use him
as a cultivation vessel
for dual cultivation,
let me have a taste first.
Then you can have your turn.
Cut the nonsense,
or I'll have the Golden Monkey bite you!
No, no!
One bite from it
will leave you hurting for hours.
His comprehension is exceptional.
According to him,
he can complete a minor circulation
of his cultivation art in one breath.
In one breath?
That's...
that's unbelievable.
But he doesn't seem like one to brag.
Records say
the first cultivators
of Shenwu Continent
date back a hundred thousand years.
Now its spiritual energy
is increasingly scarce.
I have a feeling
the great tribulation is coming.
We must restart the continent
to restore its spiritual energy.
Otherwise,
even True Immortals like us
may not survive.
The Heavenly Dao runs in cycles.
The great tribulation is coming.
There's no escaping it.
We just happened to live in this era.
But somehow,
doesn't the Heavenly Dao
always leave a way out?
A way out?
Where is the way out?
It's so hard to find.
We've lived for over a thousand years,
yet haven't found
a single Dao companion.
Are we really
going to perish
in this great tribulation
and become nourishment
for heaven and earth?
Darn.
Getting here
took us ten days drifting at sea.
We nearly capsized several times.
Will we run into Zhao Feiyang again?
Someone brought him in.
He must've been here for some time.
Don't mention him!
Just hearing that brat makes me mad.
If I ever run into him again,
I'll kill him myself!
And this island
isn't hospitable at all!
We're prodigies, after all.
Yet no one even came to greet us!
Jiang Cheng,
this is Sword Immortal Island.
Watch your mouth.
Can't I even complain?
If we weren't here to learn,
who'd come to this dump...?
Greetings, Immortal Venerables.
The most talented one has left.
Is there any point
wasting our time on them?
We can't let them
come all this way for nothing.
We still have to show
the major factions some respect.
Rise.
Thank you, Immortal Venerables!
The five of you came here
to seek instruction.
Unfortunately,
we don't have much time
to spend teaching you.
How far you go
will depend on yourselves.
We await your guidance,
Immortal Venerables!
I didn't expect to see an old friend.
If you want it back,
I will gladly return it.
Since it's yours now,
it was meant to be.
Keep it.
Thank you, Immortal Venerable Canglan.
That's a Heaven-Mending Stone,
the hardest material in existence.
Yet a single sword strike
actually left marks on it.
All right.
Go study these marks.
Sword Immortals,
what do these three marks mean?
The Dao gives birth to One.
One gives birth to Two.
Two gives birth to Three.
Three gives birth to all things.
These three marks
contain our lifelong sword intent.
You have seven days.
As for what you can learn
from these marks,
that depends on your fortune.
Looks like these three marks
contain the ultimate Sword Dao.
I see.
Thanks for your guidance,
Immortal Venerable!
Thank you, Immortal Venerable!
We shouldn't just sit around.
Let's enter secluded cultivation.
Secluded cultivation again?
How boring.
First, to prevent the demon race
from invading again.
Second,
to find a way
to face the great tribulation.
When the Heavenly Dao's
great tribulation comes,
all things are but straw dogs.
However advanced our cultivation,
how could we resist it?
Why don't we travel around for now
and enjoy the scenery?
Do you want to see the scenery
or handsome men?
Senior Sister,
if you see through someone,
don't say it out loud.
Don't you know that?
In the face of the great tribulation,
we're as powerless as ants.
But we can't just wait
for the axe to fall.
You're right, Second Senior Sister.
Let's go.
I'm finally off the island.
It's time to throw those leeches
out of our home.
I'm so used to being poor
that I actually planned to walk.
I may be at the
Minor Perfection Realm now,
but it'd still take
twenty or thirty days
to get back on foot.
Better spend some spirit crystals
to take a cloudship.
What the hell?
To whoever set up this Maze Formation,
I wandered in by mistake.
Please let me through.
In that case...
A piece of cake.
Ah, good wine!
Heavenly Mystic Robe?
Do you really have to do this?
What choice do I have?
You little brat!
You drained my spirit vein
and think you can just walk away?
What else could I do?
Wait around for you to come after me?
Fair enough.
But did you really think
you could get away from me?
So there's no room for negotiation?
There is,
of course.
All you have to do is pay
two million spirit crystals.
Then you're free to go.
Two million spirit crystals?
Why don't you just rob me?
Besides,
you already extorted so much
from those five.
Why are you coming after me too?
Well...
You really have no shame!
Those five
were merely taking the blame for you.
Your debt is a separate matter,
isn't it?
(This old man is definitely powerful.)
(I won't get the better of him.)
Senior,
two million is too much.
I can't come up with that much now.
A hundred thousand.
A hundred thousand spirit crystals.
I can barely afford that.
Huh?
Really?
Yep.
I remember
your storage ring
held plenty of spirit crystals,
along with lots of treasures
and magic boxes.
Put them all together
and they're worth well over two million.
Did you lose them?
Looks like I was right.
Come on.
Hand them over.
(His divine sense is powerful.)
(He can actually project
his divine sense)
(into my storage ring.)
(Am I really going to
hand it all over like this?)
What if I can't give it to you?
What do you mean, can't?
You mean you won't, right?
Then I'll take it myself!
♪I once stood on high,
drawing spiritual energy into my blade♪
♪I laughed, pointing at the stars,
young and fearless♪
♪Then came my fall,
with frost and snow on my shoulders♪
♪My Dao foundation was damaged,
yet my Dao heart never wavered♪
♪I crossed countless peaks
to find my answer again♪
♪Through endless trials,
my Nascent Soul came♪
♪Heaven and earth my furnace,
I rose from the flame♪
♪No sword in hand,
yet numberless blades obey♪
♪I seek the Dao beyond the clouds♪
♪Unafraid of countless trials♪
♪With this flesh and soul♪
♪I shall forge a new age♪
♪Let thunder and fire crown me♪
♪Let wind and clouds heed me♪
♪At cultivation's peak♪
♪My first resolve remains unchanged♪
♪The sun and moon turn♪
♪I hear the Great Dao ring♪
♪I am the undying flame♪
♪Looking back when dust settles♪
♪At last I see, immortality♪
♪Lives in your smiles♪